JASON NOVA

Writer & Consultant

SKILLS

- Programmer: with expertise in C++ and Python.
- Writer: with a focus on journalism, tech, and copy.
- Language: Native English, N3 Japanese.

ABOUT

I am a writer and strategic consultant with over six years of independent journalistic writing and political analysis experience. I also have four years of programming expertise in C++ and Python. My client's jobs touch domains ranging from Android development to interpreting nation-state actions.

I respond quickly and look to give my clients the best results. My writing represents honest and original opinions or analyses.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance, Online - Writer/Editor/Consultant

August 2014 - June 2017

- I have worked for companies such as Android Authority and The Mukt.
- Helped coordinate the <u>Linux section</u> of an online news aggregate.
- Brought in over 100k views and 3000+ comments on a single article.

The Toreadors, Woodland Hills CA, USA - Opinion Editor

August 2011 - June 2013

- I managed the renewal of the paper's entire technology lineup.
- Over two years I turned the newspaper into a respectable source of news.

EDUCATION

Santa Monica College, Santa Monica CA, USA

August 2014 - December 2016

I was the Vice President of the largest international club in the school and helped promote mental health and cultural integration.

AWARDS

Cambridge College Summer Program | Paris Architectural Study Award